Beyond Hope. Beyond Regret. Beyond Salvation.
Diablo is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Lawrence Roeck.
A young civil war veteran is forced on a desperate
journey to save his kidnapped wife.
Jackson, played by Scott Eastwood.
Ezra, played by Walton Goggins.
Alexsandra, played by Camilla Belle.
Benjamin Carver, played by Danny Glover.
Nakoma, played by Adam Beach.
Quok Mi, played by Tzi Ma.
Diablo is a 2015 revisionist Western psychological thriller film produced, co-written and directed by
Lawrence Roeck, and starring Scott Eastwood, Walton Goggins, Camilla Belle and Danny Glover.
It was the first western film starring Scott Eastwood, the
younger son of Western icon Clint Eastwood.
It was released on January 8, 2016 by Orion Pictures and Momentum Pictures.
The tone is intense.